(Sheldon:)but then I realized what
(Sheldon:)I really want to ask you is
(Sheldon:)just can you just go?
(Sheldon:)You're healthy.
(Sheldon:)You have a job in the sciences.
(Sheldon:)I've got to say, if this
credit report comes back good,
(Sheldon:)you're the frontrunner.
(Amy(on Skype):)I'm not gonna be
your roommate, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)But I met with 11 people,
(Sheldon:)and they all walked out.
And that Hollywood phony
Chris Pratt
(Sheldon:)never tweeted me back.
(Amy:)I'm sure you'll find
somebody else.
(Sheldon:)I suppose.
(Sheldon:)What happened to me, Amy?
(Sheldon:)Years ago I was
(Sheldon:)completely disengaged
from my feelings.
(Sheldon:)I'd say it was a happier time,
(Sheldon:)but I was disengaged from
my feelings, so who can tell?
(Amy:)I don't know how to help you.
(Leonard:)You know,
feelings are a part of life.
(Sheldon:)They didn't used to be.
(Sheldon:)You and Leonard and Penny,
(Sheldon:)you all poisoned me
with emotions.
(Sheldon:)I was like the Tin Man,
perfectly content
(Sheldon:)until that evil Wizard
gave him a heart.